When I got this offer, the biggest thing I said was that I was really happy.
I'm an idol, not a model or anything like that.
I'm not a model or anything, but I'm really happy to be able to walk on the runway.
I'm really happy.
Rehearsal. From now on.
I was more nervous at the rehearsal than at the show.
I'm so nervous. I'm so nervous.
I'm the kind of person who worries about what other people think.
At times like that, I'm doing my best to make sure that today will be over.
Let's always be members of the same love group.
Don't change yourself too much.
Tell yourself that nervousness is a good thing.
I'm so nervous and so nervous, but at the same time, I'm enjoying it.
Rehearsal is over.
I'm going to take off my shoes.
I hadn't worn heels for a long time.
So I was afraid I'd fall down.
Surprisingly, I was fine.
So, I usually wear heels like this.
Like this? No?
But I don't have the strength to sit on my neck, and my hands are like this,
So today, I feel like this.
I want to walk like this.
It looks delicious.
Flowers would be jealous.
Ah! Thank you.
Hana loves curry.
If she eats all this, she might never go in there again.
She was always very young to be in front of people.
I got him to sing, and that made me realize how much I like music, I was singing and I liked the music,
I was pretty much in the groove,
But if you ask me if I could do that in front of people, I don't think so.
I never wanted to perform in front of people at school recitals.
He was the kind of person who would have said, "If that's the case, I'll just have to go through the training,
It wasn't just a beautiful thing,
I was really troubled inside and cried,
There were many times when I was really troubled and cried and felt like I was being crushed,
So, once I got over it, I felt like I didn't want to leave the house.
I didn't want to leave the house.
I didn't want to go out of the house, or I didn't want to be in public.
There was a time when I wanted to quit.
People don't want to quit too much now.
Family and friends support you unconditionally, don't they?
But even people I don't know, people I've never met...
They tell me to do my best, but it's not often that I can cheer them on from the bottom of my heart.
And yet, there are so many fans who support me and Ameflash.
If I get a little sick or something...
I'm sure you'd be looking forward to our live shows and so on.
I know you're looking forward to our gigs.
Not that I was looking forward to it.
Just take your time and I'll be waiting for you.
I only have fans who are kind enough to wait for me.
When I think about them...
I really want to go back.
No matter how much I get discouraged
I want to stand in front of you again.
I want to return the favor.
I want to grow more and more like a candy flash
I'd like to be able to see a better view.I guess you could call it an easy-to-see view.
Show me how you've grown.
Because I want to spread the candy flash.
I want to have something good.
I want to go back to it.
You know what?
This is not the place for that.
This is the back side of the new runway.
You can't come in here.
Walk with confidence.
I'm going to do my best to be able to say, "Who is that girl?
I'm nervous around here.
Don't finish.
I don't know why I get more nervous during rehearsals.
But if I don't stand up for the performance with the feeling that I am the best, my lack of confidence in my life will be obvious.
It shows on my face, so I think it's a difference in my mindset.
It was fun.
I usually only sing and dance on stage like that,
It was almost the first time for me to put on clothes and walk around with confidence that I was the best.
It was my second time, so I was very nervous, but it was fun.
There were some things I wanted to do better,
I would like to do my best next time if I have the chance.
I'm scared.
Are you okay? Thank you very much.
Are you okay?
I'm a little catty.
Gentle.
Cat bumpy.
Thank you.
Thank you, too.Thank you very much.
Was it cute?
Then it's OK.
Thank you for your hard work.